<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Christopher Fu</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Christopher Fu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 16:12:06 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Code Geass S1</title>
      <link>http://example.org/anime/code-geass-s1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/anime/code-geass-s1/</guid>
      <description>Code Geass is well-known in the anime world for being one of the greats. I&amp;rsquo;ve never had the opportunity myself to watch it before, for various reasons&amp;mdash;it aired in 2006, I don&amp;rsquo;t usually go out of my way to watch mecha, the character design isn&amp;rsquo;t really up my alley&amp;mdash;but after doing so, I can definitely see why this series is so highly regarded.
Art: 2/4 There&amp;rsquo;s nothing too special about the art in Code Geass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A (Mostly) Jargon-Free Glossary of Programming Terms</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/programming-glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 20:25:05 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/programming-glossary/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents A C D F H L M N R S V
A   abstraction: A way of thinking about a problem that makes it easier to reason about. For example, say we want to write a program that fetches some data from a server. We might write a function that abstracts away the nitty-gritty details of actually making the request, handling errors in case the server is down, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code Geass Ep. 23-24</title>
      <link>http://example.org/anime/code-geass-23-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 18:29:46 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/anime/code-geass-23-24/</guid>
      <description>Things I liked:
 The killing off of Euphemia was done well, even if the events leading up to it were sort of contrived (it seems weird that Lelouch would bring up &amp;ldquo;killing all Japanese&amp;rdquo; out of nowhere). It really raises the stakes now. CC&amp;rsquo;s mecha pilot outfit looks nice.  Cornelia&amp;rsquo;s betrayal: Classic plot twist done nicely.  Things I didn&amp;rsquo;t like:
 I never noticed this before, but Kallen&amp;rsquo;s mecha pilot outfit looks outrageous:  I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what the Britannian military&amp;rsquo;s plan is with using Lancelot.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>